<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Informatique on Les Tribulations de Stella en Signes</title><link>https://stella-hoshineko.github.io/tags/informatique/</link><description>Recent content in Informatique on Les Tribulations de Stella en Signes</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>fr-fr</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://stella-hoshineko.github.io/tags/informatique/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Back From the Dead - A GitHub Story</title><link>https://stella-hoshineko.github.io/posts/24-06-14-still-alive/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stella-hoshineko.github.io/posts/24-06-14-still-alive/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m Alive Hi there, it&amp;rsquo;s me again, your fave walking disaster, Stella. It&amp;rsquo;s sure been a while.
Since my last post roughly 9 months ago, I&amp;rsquo;ve been offered a postdoc in Israel (which I reluctantly accepted due to a lack of alternative options), cancelled said postdoc weeks before departure (due to the still-very-much-ongoing genocide in Gaza), ended up homeless in the process (still an open problem) as well as unemployed (this one has been kinda solved recently, for a while at least), started outing myself as autistic at work, went through another deep depressive episode during the winter (to the point of worrying my therapist), became a baby mod on a beloved Discord server and am now in the process of starting HRT (at-long-fucking-last, some will say).</description></item><item><title>Bliss Stage : l'enfer, c'est les Autres</title><link>https://stella-hoshineko.github.io/posts/23-08-23-bliss/</link><pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://stella-hoshineko.github.io/posts/23-08-23-bliss/</guid><description>J&amp;rsquo;ai eu il y a quelques années l&amp;rsquo;occasion de jouer au jeu de rôle Bliss Stage. J&amp;rsquo;avais plutôt apprécié l&amp;rsquo;expérience, mais le manuel de jeu n&amp;rsquo;est plus officiellement édité, est devenu assez introuvable en VF, et contient des ajouts exclusifs (absents de l&amp;rsquo;édition originale dans la langue de Bernie Sanders). Lorsque j&amp;rsquo;ai enfin pu mettre la main dessus, j&amp;rsquo;ai naturellement fait de mon mieux pour produire un scan aussi propre que possible avec les moyens du bord :</description></item></channel></rss>